{"basic": {
      "001": {
            "front": "Cubic zirconia is a synthesized material often used in place of what precious stone?",
            "back": "Diamond"
      },
      "002": {
            "front": "In what year did the Titanic sink?",
            "back": "1912"

      },
      "003": {
            "front": "What sunglasses did Tom Cruise where in the 1986 movie 'Top Gun'?",
            "back": "Ray Ban Aviator (RB 3025)"

      },
      "004": {
            "front": "How many Olympic Games have been hosted in Africa?",
            "back": "Zero"

      },
      "005": {
            "front": "What takes an average of 8 minutes 20 seconds to reach the Earth?",
            "back": "Sunlight"

      }
},

"clozed": {
      "001": {
            "front": "... is a synthesized material often used in place of diamond.",

            "back": "Cubic zirconia"
      },
      "002": {
            "front": "The Titanic sank in the year of ... .",
            "back": "1912"

      },
      "003": {
            "front": "Tom Cruise wore ... sunglasses in the 1986 movie 'Top Gun'.",
            "back": "Ray Ban Aviator (RB 3025)"

      },
      "004": {
            "front": "... Olympic Games have been hosted in Africa.",
            "back": "Zero"

      },
      "005": {
            "front": "... takes an average of 8 minutes 20 seconds to reach the Earth.",
            "back": "Sunlight"

      }
}
}